## **Meseret Haddis**

meseretfh@gmail.com 303 Pacific Ave Jersey City, NJ 07304

<u>linktr.ee/meziszem</u>

Edit/VFX Reel - <u>vimeo.com/382338722</u> (pass: diamondwar) Color Reel - <u>vimeo.com/796472002</u> (pass: lean4reel)

### **SUMMARY**

Video editor and producer of creative digital and social media with over 10 years of experience looking to create engaging content that always entertains. Well versed in post-production practices using Adobe Suite and Davinci Resolve programs and project managing numerous deliverables at a time. Technical background in production working with cinema camera equipment and educational experience crafting scripts and treatments.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

#### MLB Network - Freelance Associate Producer

03/2022 to Present

- -Creating unique and engaging highlights and in-bumps using Adobe Premiere and After Effects that adhere to brand guidelines and executing with tight turnaround times.
- -Continual communication with Supervising Producers and Junior Editors to ensure quality control and timely delivery.

## **Various Clients - Freelance Colorist**

08/2021 to Present

- -Worked with DP's and editors to adhere to brand specifications regarding look, tone and consistency for color grading.
- -Provided assistance and troubleshooted video issues like incorrect white balance, under/over exposed lighting and composite fixes using Davinci Resolve.

### The Muse - Video Editor

09/2016 to 03/2020

- -Crafting sharp and engaging doc-styled videos like a Japanese language testimonial for WeWork in Japan where subtitles, translation services, and client feedback had to be managed.
- -Improved production process to include unused media and increase client value from our products.
- -Engaged with brand and social media guidelines to produce content that reflected client's values to be delivered to internal platforms and Youtube/Instagram.

### **EDUCATION**

# **New York University - Tisch School of the Arts**

08/2008 to 05/2010

-Majored in Dramatic Writing with an emphasis on TV Writing.